allow me to pray heavenly father thank
you you are a
warrior there's no battle you have ever
lost may this be a conviction in our
hearts that your children as we all go
through different
circumstances that are horrifying
purifying
threatening give your children
sleep to be able to sleep a peaceful
sleep of perfect
trust help our
unbelief and grow our faith to always
consider moving forward no matter the
circumstances that surround us knowing
that you are in full
control this
evening yet again we are here to sit at
your feet and feed from your
word May the Holy Spirit take these
words Pierce them in our hearts like
arrows to cause a conviction and to
[Music]
conversion this is our prayer in Jesus
holy
name
amen the book is
job
before the crown must SC the
cross I have entitled today's
suon when God is proud of
you when
God is proud of
you move with me to chapter one of
job verse
6 Job chapter
1 verse 6
now there was a
day when the sons of
God came to present themselves before
the
Lord and Satan also came among
them and the Lord said to
Satan from
where do you
come so Satan answered the Lord and said
from going to and from on the
earth and from walking back and forth on
it I want you to notice these are not
human beings having a
conversation God is
Spirit the devil is
Spirit demons are Spirit
angels are Spirit beings so these are
Spirit beings not in the Physical Realm
but in the realm of the spirit having a
what a
discussion the conversation
continues then the Lord said to Satan
verse 8 have you considered my servant
job
that there is none like him on us God is
bragging about
Job there's none like him on earth a
blameless and upright
man one who fears
God and shuns evil whatever that
statement meant I do not know but if job
was living in our time what is our
population to today 7 billion
plus there's none like job among 7
billion plus
people and I would confirm to you even
when you think the whole world is
corrupt God's children are still
there when you think all marriages don't
work it is yours that does not work
their marriage is working in this
world you can't throw up your hands and
say after all marriage today doesn't
work which
one you only know
viewers elah at some point almost gave
up says I alone I'm what what did the
Lord say yeah you think you're alone how
many more do we have that have not bowed
down to B
it could be a corrupt
Church never move out of this church
because you think it's
rotten when Noah built the ark and they
went in eight people with all the
animals all sorts of animals you could
think
of and they were there for many days
many
days I think it was a year plus
I go study your Bible well it was a year
plus many
days I'll go and counter check be like
the bans
study they're not there for a short time
in the
ark that is where they
stayed that is where they helped
themselves relieved themselves me I
don't know if there was some drainage
system I don't know but you can imagine
those of us that keep Gods at home have
you ever opened forgot to leave that
their house how do you call that house
the a it's called a yes have you ever
opened forgots a in the morning it
stinks but they had to stay there for
all those days because that was the only
place where salvation could be found
outside there was
nothing this church is the Ark of God it
smells it stinks if you run away there's
no salvation out there it is where it is
here this is a hospital for every sick
child of God so don't come here with
very high expectations about the
children of God
so is not your business to start
questioning what is she doing in our
church she has come to God's
Church God's
hospital so the world is still
full of people that God can point and
say this one is mine even when you think
you cannot see them so it will be it it
will be a lie to say that all men are
the same unless you have slept with all
of
them lived with all of them the only man
you know is your husband apart from the
women that have three four
men so you can't just be looking at any
man you meet in church you are the same
you are the same
amidst so much
corruption children of God still
exist they
there so Satan answered the Lord and
said does job fear you fear God for
nothing so he thinks job is the type
that worships God for the things God has
given he thinks job is the type that is
interested in the gifts of of God than
the
giver it's unfortunate many of us we are
here for the gifts we are not here for
the what for The Giver of the gifts it's
unfortunate and the Lord knows all of us
even when you still want to say I am a
church member I've come to church God
knows our hearts he knows whether you've
come to seek him or you have come to
seek his gifts
have you not made a hge around him
around his
household and around all that he has on
every side you have blessed the work of
his hands and his possessions have
increased in the land but now stretch
out your hand and touch all that he has
and he will surely cast you to your
face and the Lord said to Satan behold
all that he has is in your power
only do not lay a hand on his person so
Satan went out from the presence of the
law the conversation between these
Spirit beings in the realm of the spirit
Ends by God giving certain permission to
torment who
job look at the confidence God has with
job that he can permit the devil to
torment his life because he's so sure
God job will never bow down to who to
the
devil there are things we go through in
this life be very careful before you
overreact you could be going through
them because God is proving to the devil
that you are actually his child
some of the sufferings we go through we
go through because God is proud of
us the cross you have to
bear is probably because God is proud of
you there's an
accusation she's excellent she's
prospering she's progressing simply
because you have built a h let me tell
you when God builds a hge of fire around
you whatever H it is no one can come
close to
you but you need to know there are times
he can pull that hedge like he pulled
out that hedge from job to permit the
devil to torment him and he was
confident enough job was not going to
let him
down can the Lord depend on you
to prove to the world that the wealth we
have whether we have it or not we can
still worship
Him can the Lord count on
you when your marriage is going down can
the Lord count on you and say oh yeah
this one believes in the institution of
marriage and so this one is able to
fight for it up to the
end can the Lord count on
you yeah this one is enjoying marriage
because God has built a hedge of fire
around her when the Lord pulls it away
can the Lord still count on you that we
will stick through no matter
what
snapped you snapped
that which you're going through chances
are listen to
me is because God has withdrawn his
protection because he's proud of you and
he has to prove to the devil that you
will never bow down before
him but many of us have failed that test
Miss is
re at times the cross we have to carry
is because God is proud of
us and we shall carry it it can be so
ugly so ugly that when you listen to
that story you wonder is that Muro
I remember at some point someone made an
ugly statement and
said when I just began to preach
actively on Family Life me I didn't know
was cut out for family me I was just
preaching and someone made a comment and
said
that was the day I went back to this
story of
job and asked
myself is there a mistake I have made I
said no I haven't made any
mistake I'm sure if job was living in
our time most of you would have said
a
sacrifice in one
day is not everything we go through
there's something wrong we have done no
at times we go through it because God is
proud of his
children and I looked at the
girl and I said who
knows your ministry is found where you
have been
broken so it's not that the MOs have
arrived they
haven't I know many people would want to
know how does Muro family look like many
people really want to
know we haven't arrived
yet we are just going strong because we
have chosen to lean on the Everlasting
Arms that's
all we understand we are not where we
ought to be but we are certainly not
where we used to
be our dysfunctions don't stop us from
talking about the strength that God has
given us to be where we
are we will move we will progress
regardless of what circumstances
surround us we're not going to stop and
stop start to M and complain life has
got to move
forward I mean
more that simply tells you life must do
what move
forward take heart God is proud of you
there's nothing wrong you have
done he's just proud of you
and the Lord said to Satan we have read
that
now there was a day before I get to
verse 13 another bit I want you to
understand
that good people also suffer bad
things did you hear what I said when you
are God's child you are not excused from
suffering I make this joke even
vegetarians can get
cancer strict vegetarians I know that
have diabetes and pressure and they say
I've never touched meat not even a men
but they have diabetes and
pressure good people also
suffer bad things when they start the
story of Jon
not John Lazarus in the Book of John
11 the Bible says that
this when the sister came is it the
sister of the disciples who came and
told Christ the one whom you
love is
sick the one whom you do what you love
is
sick let me tell you something about K
Martha's home Martha and Mary magdal
plus their brother
Lazarus that was one home where Christ
would sleep eat
birth it was like his home when he was
tired and he needed a place to rest he
would go to whose home it is a home he
operated like it was
theirs with freedom with ease have you
gotten into someone's house as a guest
and you've became so so comfortable like
it's your home yeah that is how he
operated in kata's
home so the one that he loved was sick
did he go
immediately did he go
immediately he
didn't in fact he left him and he did
what he
died good people suffer what bad thing
but even when you have to suffer bad
things listen to me carefully God is
still
God he hasn't
changed don't be the kind that praises
the Lord because there are good things
happening in your life and when bad
things begin to happen you begin to
doubt whether he exists or not God has
nothing to lose even when you die today
he has nothing to do what to lose
because God looks at life beyond what
you see on Earth God has a more better
and greater life to give you than this
which you have today so even if you died
today he has nothing to
lose there are people we have prayed
with pleaded with God preserve this life
we have done prayers fasted and they
have ended up dying it does
not mean that the Lord has ceased to be
the
Lord he still Reigns Supreme
he doesn't need to show up when you need
him he can go silent on you until you
die he went silent on John the Baptist
the same guy who said Behold the Lamb of
God takes away the sin of the world now
he's in prison he's asking go ask him is
he the Messiah we were waiting for why
because he has not come to save
him and Christ says go tell him the
those that are lame are walking those
that are blind are seeing what was
Christ
saying I mean John you are born for one
purpose as a forerunner to prepare the
way for me now I have come you have no
more reason to do what to leave you have
emptied yourself of your full potential
you have fulfilled your purpose in life
so even if you die right now I have
nothing to lose the is a Bigg and better
life that I have prepared for
you and do you think You' if you've
accepted Christ he must be doing you a
favor every day Christianity is not
about God doing you
favors so we can't worship God because
he's a
giver no and you're only interested in
his gifts we will worship him whether he
shows up or he goes
silent so for some of us when he goes
silent you now look for some witch
doctor when he goes silent you now look
for a witch doctor because it's witch
doctors that speak immediately
you want things that are instant yes God
why am I going through this you want to
understand so when God keeps silent what
do you do
sure
Tanzania and once you're from Tanzania
you'll come back to your house and KN
and hey God I did know go that far
forgive me then you come to church on
Sabbath but you see in the house there's
some water you were given there's some
charm powder water you were given
some sticks
tied times a woman can put a very tiny
stick rolled with some red I don't know
why they love red some red thread very
tiny insert it at the Hem of your
trouser I tell you even if you want to
go where you will not go you just
revolve
they put
it because you know you're the one who's
asking them what to put
on so she gives you the the stick is
already at the Hem of the
trouser so even if you want to go where
just you just go around you go back say
I want to go somewhere you go and for
sure you've left your you'll just go
around town come back
home I want to go see my mother you'll
just
back to the house and one year goes down
the line two years 3 4 5 10 you have
never gone home to see your
mother because a woman has tied you
down this is the same thing that strange
women do to people's husbands they just
tie you like
that and at times when the Lord says
enough is
enough and that person goes up to their
houses I'm speaking to women whose
husbands have been taken don't just be
happy he has come kneel down kneel
down kneel down and bind and rebuke
every form of evil and darkness that has
come with this person because he has not
come empty he has come
loaded just in case he gets home where
that woman doesn't want him to get just
in case he gets there
goes
back cuz you you're fighting a physical
Warfare when it gets tough the tough
gets going to God even when he remains
silent keep going to who to
God some of these things you engaging
you will find some relief for you you
the visitor to the witch doctor but you
bind all your generations to the curses
that come with it that is what we are
suffering today most of us our lives
cannot move because our fathers our
mothers our grandparents visited altars
of
evil we are now suffering those
cures and at times I come with mine from
my my from kindu I come with my
generational cures moo comes with his
gener
cures from M now they will say they'll
do a biography saying moo comes
[Music]
from and we meet in our
house and then the house becomes
unbearable we begin to fight and we
don't understand why we were fighting
each other it is generational C is doing
what playing out and if you don't learn
to look at it with a spiritual eye you
will begin to react and overreact on
things that are beyond your what Your
control and lose your
marriage learn to break generational
curses even you sited here I know you
are visited you know I'm telling you you
are ruining your
entire generations to come you sit you
love it
you love
it cuz you know how to protect yourself
say you see what my children this is
what they say for those that for those
that have not entered it so much they
say where we stay there are too many
witches so they need they also need
something to protect them themselves
that is what they say then they go to
the witch doctor to protect their
children to protect their homes and very
innocent children you'll be cut cut
if you look at your wife and you see
three
marks then some powder
is I've seen some they cut here is it
some people cut
here some cut here some is the
stomach they're protecting their
children wait when these children grow
up and you see how turmoil
Reigns in their life because their
children sacrificed to the altars of
what
evil nothing
moves even when God is silent you would
rather die in that Silence with the hope
of the Resurrection
morning learn to look at life beyond
this
life look at life with eternal interests
I have nothing to lose
if the worst comes to the worst there's
a better home waiting for
me but we want to live like this is the
end of life this is where we stay
forever such that today when you preach
when you preach Christ is coming you
will be told you are an
alist you are an
extremist people don't want to hear that
Christ is coming
oh you don't need to do this because
Christ is no Christ I wouldn't lie to
you listen to me very
carefully Christ is at the
door but that doesn't mean life stops he
says occupy till I
come we were not to wait Christ for
Christ in
idleness we were to wait wa for Christ
engaged in
activities not in
idleness wherever he'll find you make
sure he finds you prepared for his
coming so when God's goes silent on you
don't be tempted to walk away from him
even when he goes silent to the point of
death don't be
tempted at you're holding your ch like
this and you can see your child dying
and someone tells
you haven't you read the little time of
trouble some of us will not bear it
haven't you read yeah the little time of
trouble coming most of us will not bear
it Ellen White says God in his grace
will decide who sleeps before that time
because he looks at your faith it is
little but it is sincere this one let me
allow it to sleep but why do we cry like
people who have no
hope some of us will have to sleep
before he comes not all of us will see
the little time of trouble not all of
us so we don't we are not afraid of
death at all
and God is still
God now there was a day when his sons
and daughters were eating and drinking
wine in their oldest brother's
house and a messenger came to job and
said The Oxen were plowing and the
donkeys feeding beside them when the
sians raided them and took them away
indeed they have killed the servants
with the ede of the sword and I alone
have escaped to tell you so job is still
processing that information all his oxen
are gone while he's still processing the
word of the Lord says while he was still
speaking not even in he had not finished
what
speaking he said while he was still
speaking another also came and said the
fire of God fell from heaven and burned
up the sheep and the servants and
consumed them and I alone have escaped
to tell you listen how people confuse
suffering from the devil to be suffering
from who God who was given permission to
to
torment job it was certain so but listen
to what the servants are saying fire
from where from
God he didn't he didn't even begin to
process that information he did not it
says while he was still
speaking another also came a third one
and said the calans formed three Burns
raided the camels and took them away yes
and killed the servants with the ede of
the sword and I alone have escaped to
tell you he has not finished while he
was still speaking another also came and
said your sons and daughters were eating
and drinking wine in their oldest
brother's house and suddenly a great
wind came from across the wilderness and
struck the four corners of the house and
it fell on the young people and they are
dead 10 children at
ago and I alone have escaped to tell
you let me drive a very strong point
home in this life don't Focus so much on
the Physical Realm
there's another realm called the
spiritual realm where Spirit beings
dwell and Paul says for we are not
fighting against flesh and what
blood but against demonic
power so he say don't waste your time on
what you can see that is not where the
war is the war is where things things
are invisible the realm of the spirit it
means therefore that by the time you see
a problem with your physical eyes it
didn't begin there where did it begin in
the realm of the spirit that is where
things are cooked and finished before
they manifest in the realm of the what
the physical because where did the war
begin the War Began in the spirit real
with the discussion between God and
Satan that is where it began
and I'm very sure job is not aware of
that discussion because no one ever told
him it is you and I who are aware
because we are reading the story I don't
know who wrote that book whatever but
job died unawares of the discussion in
the realm of the spirit but he still
served his God with all his
heart by the time you see trouble in
your life like this with your own eyes
because that is what is physical
stand it didn't begin that time it is a
plot that has been already cooked and
completed in the realm of the what
spirit so don't fight
people you don't fight your husband you
don't fight your wife you don't fight
your children you don't fight colleagues
in the office no don't fight the person
you see that is a conduit of the
devil there's a power that actuates them
they have become an agency of the devil
to fulfill his schemes in the realm of
the What Spirit nothing just happens it
was planned first before it was
implemented so don't waste your time
fighting where the implementation takes
place spend time fighting where the
planning takes place where the cooking
takes place move into the real of the
spirit shut down the devil there before
he can
manifest in the
physical and up to now you're still
wasting time fighting in the physical
oh before you can approach a spouse and
ask them why they're doing the things
they doing first of all diminish the
Demonic power in them in the realm of
the What Spirit diminish it completely
then now talk to them you'll be talking
to a sober person before you do that
you'll be talking to a woman that will
give you one
answer you will not come back again
because that is not them there's a power
in
them so we must sit and
talk not all things require
conversation some things require battle
in the spirit realm that battle will
produce its effects in the
physical because when you fight there
you will see the effect where here isn't
it Moses that went to fight in the realm
of the spirit with Aon and Ur and he
says when he lifted up his hands what
was happening down here they
won it is the activities at the hill
that were informing activities where
down
here and for as long as your prayer
closet is inactive expect nothing to
happen physically it will still be
turmoil War for as long as you're not
praying and let no one cheat you that
they can pray for
you we don't pray for
people we pray with
people why when Moses hand got tired he
did not tell Aaron let me rest now you
come and do
what it was not aon's responsibility it
was purely
Moses's and so Moses still had the
responsibility of keeping his hand up
the others just came to support the
battle you're going through is not
muro's responsibility it's yours you
must keep your hand
up when you get tired now call on moo
and say moo my hand is getting tired put
a stone that I may sit and lift my hand
so this business of people coming to
church refusing to grow their spiritual
lives and believing that until someone
prays for
them let me tell you even if we pray for
you and you don't pray still nothing
will
happen laziness your Christianity happy
Sabbath praise the Lord God is good that
is what is easy for you when you're f
with the battle and we are seeing there
is now no time to sleep people are eov
the enemy has attacked you you want to
sleep
Pastor you remember me with my
family as you sleep 8 hours because
doctor said an adult should do 8
hours there's no problem you can even do
10 but you can't do 10 when the enemy
has done what attacked your home is
under attack and you can afford to how
do you expect to win Warfare you are
under serious
attack8
hours doctor said you must have
rest there is time to rest and there's
time to fight when the Lord will give
you rest from all your Wars then you can
rest but when the enemy has attacked you
can't sleep do you know how they built
the wall of Jerusalem do you know one
hand had a what a weapon another one was
doing what Bing
[Music]
to8
hours bad light let me tell you
something about the devil the devil
knows the things that work to bring him
down so he takes them
I started fasting do I look
sholic it is meant to kill your
confidence in the very activities
spiritual that God has asked us to do
fasting is a spiritual
necessity for you to thrive because that
is the only way you p penetrate and go
into the realm of the spirit there's no
other
way the church has its program good I
have no problem and the church does that
to remind you you should not be sleeping
you should be fasting but I'm telling
you when you get into fasting you
saturate yourself with the power of
God you become spiritually sensitive so
I'm asking why should someone determine
for you when to
fast the church is simply reminding you
there's something called fasting but you
don't need to
wait until the first Sabbath of every
quarter to fast and there is war raging
in your what your
house and even when that first Sabbath
come you come to learn about it that
Sabbath
diabet
inter fting
sh losing weight should be a product of
fasting but it should not be the
object
fasting so if you still want to wait for
someone to determine for you when you
want to saturate yourself with strength
and the devil is working 24/7 to make
sure he takes you down
this is not shakah
FAS shakah fasting to seek Christ is it
this is not we are not fasting to seek
Christ we are fasting to fight you don't
fight battles forever is it
yeah and don't think when you fast you
will untwist God's hand you can't I've
fasted why haven't I seen a
change everyone has a Wilderness
experience and the Lord determines how
long you take
there for Israel it was 430 years in
Egypt in bondage no amount of fasting
was going to reduce it fasting would
only strengthen them to finish those
years so you don't fast to un twist God
you first to get strength to continue
with a
war because every single day is a
countdown to Victory if God a portioned
you will be there 20 years every single
day reduces the 20
years and you need that strength
so in one
day job lost his
children his
wealth his
status one
day he had to bury 10
children I don't think
there's anyone in this world who has
come anything anywhere close to what job
went through no one no one no
one when the Lord permits something to
come your way he's so sure you can bear
it he
can if he allows your wife to die he
knows you can can bu
it if he allows that you're widowed at
23 he knows you can
bu and I know some women will tell you
by
way there are times there are
women you're only 26 you already have
four children you've not even finished
morning team so they want to
rationalize how a human being feels and
grows and develops and give you an
advice I know of people that God has
shut down those
feelings completely and they never even
think of it and they're raising children
in the absence of their husbands and
they have kept their husband's name and
a home to
dat today
because
[Music]
in fact she has full support
from that home that is the day you will
hear them
[Music]
say you're better off single because he
knows the complexities that come with it
so
how will you satisfy your sexual
[Music]
then it means he was shocked
I don't know for how long he sat there
but the Bible says then he
arose I'm very sure where he was seated
he was
thinking you mean I can serve God like
this and he
permited he was struggling with a lot of
thoughts
there is nothing wrong with the struggle
of thoughts in your mind there's nothing
wrong it is normal it is normal to
question why God permitted it it is
normal but don't question to the point
you begin to doubt
him and go job questioned so many things
in his mind and the Bible says when he
processed
everything then
he
arose and when he
arose he didn't rise to complain or mama
no when job arose he
said when he arose he tore his robe
shaved his head he fell to the ground
and
worshiped he didn't fall to the ground
to cry he fell to the ground to do what
was he was saying God no matter what I
will still worship you no matter what I
will never bow down my knee to B no
matter what I will not trade the path to
endure no matter what I will never
decide I'm going to see some someone who
prays for people in K's
Lambs said no matter what I may not
understand I am still worshiping
you because you're still God
worshiped and he said naked I came from
my mother's womb and naked shall I
return there the lord gave and the Lord
has taken away blessed be the name of
the
Lord listen to verse 22 the last one in
all this job did not sin nor charge god
with what
wrong why are you afraid to
lose your property
why why you holding on to it so tightly
that you're so scared to lose it you
can't find peace when you lose it
why are you
scared at times we fight over homes that
we want to build I have no trouble
whether you build a 10 bedroom home but
we don't need to fight about it even if
you give me a one bedroom house you gave
me me I'm waiting for the new Heaven and
the new Earth where we shall build and
stay
in
them learn to look at life in light of
Eternity this is not our
home it is
not it is
not all these things we cling
to the Lord will clean them up with fire
all
telling you
all all these vehicles we drive someone
now will say she is beginning to preach
extremism that people should not drive
all these vehicles we drive all the Lord
will clear them with fire there is
nothing in this earth that we shall go
with to where to
Heaven if the Lord permits that we lose
them for circumstances Beyond us to
understand do not forsake God bow down
to
worship if there's a moment you should
worship God it is in your worst
moment someone has sung a song I'm not a
good singer for the god of the
mountains is still go in the
valley when things go
wrong he'll make them
right for the god of the good
times is still God in the bad
times the god of the
[Music]
day is still God in the
night he's still
God he has nothing to
lose if you sleep
today there's a better life
coming if you never have the wealth of
this life there's a greater inheritance
awaiting
you provided you don't bow down to
worship
Satan I pray no matter what we go
through we will never worship Satan
whatsoever Heavenly
Father this is not our
home but there's a life to live
as we await your second
coming we are bombarded on every
side there seems not to be rest for
us it is one thing after the other like
job when we're just recovering from one
battle the devil introduces another one
give us the
strength to
endure to
persevere until we get used to
suffering until we care no more whether
it is there or
not but we are determined to let the
world of Darkness know no matter what we
go through we will never Bow Down down
and worship the
devil will still worship you in good
times and in bad
times even when we walk through the
valley of the shadow of death we will
still worship
you even though we walk through the
waters we will still Worship
You Through the Fire we will still
worship you
Han M andaria
say we will not bow down for we know the
Lord we serve will deliver us and even
if he does
not it does not reduce him from being
God he is still Our God we will not
worship B
lift our thoughts away from this world
and its
things lift our
thoughts from thinking that this is our
home may we learn to look at things in
light of
Eternity at times you will go silent on
us you are still
God there's a season for
everything there's a time we will have
there's a time we will lack you're still
God and we are
excited and comforted to know that some
of these things we go through is because
you're proud of
us and so we shall Carry the Cross
with a lot of joy in our
hearts with a lot of
confidence with a Victorious
fortitude knowing that it doesn't matter
to us how long it will
take for you're not controlled by time
and
space we will bear our suffering with a
lot of Joy with a lot of patience with a
lot of perseverance because God still
Reigns may your will be
there May your children be comforted
with these
words may they find peace in their heart
as they go
home may they move forward with life
knowing you are taking care of their
mess may they wake up with strength
knowing the circumstances that surround
them is purely God's to deal
with
tonight someone has never
slept give them a peaceful sleep of
perfect Trust
tonight someone has never
healed from whatever circumstances they
went through there's so much bitterness
and anger inside there's
resentment
tonight replace it with the spirit of
forgiveness there's one who's been
tormented by demonic power and have
never found peace in their lives they
can't sleep in the night they dream bad
dreams things walk in their
bodies phenomenon explained to anyone no
one can
understand some people will sink their
alucin
tonight give them rest from the powers
of
Darkness it is my
prayer oh
God
that you will visit each one of us at a
very personal
level and when you
visit you visit and never in
vain whatever you want it to accomplish
it will to the glory and honor of your
name give us peace that surpasseth all
understanding to gu our minds and to gu
our
hearts and may your name forever be
glorified as we await for your second
coming to reign with you in the new
heavens and the new Earth this is our
prayer by faith in Jesus holy name am